Abolfazl Ghorbani Front End Developer

Kiel, Germany DOB: 17.02.1980

Phone: +4915215269803

Email: ab.ghorbani28@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abolfazl-ghorbani

Github: https://github.com/ab-prog1

Research gate: https://researchgate.net/profile/Abolfazl-Ghorbani-2

SUMMRY

Reliable, flexible and disciplined front-end developer in developing web apps. highly adaptive to new challenges and responsibilities. Experienced in working to tight deadlines and under time pressure while ensuring quality. I look forward to opportunities where i can contribute my skills and collaborate with a team to create quality projects.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, jQuery, HTML, SQL/MySQL

Stylesheet: CSS, Sass, styled-components

Technologies: React.js, Redux, Next.js, Axios, SWR, Bootstrap, Ajax, Postman

Familiarties: PHP, Laravel, Node.js

Other tools: Git/Github, Microsoft Office

Network: windows, Linux, Network+, windows server, DNS, DHCP, Active Directory, CCNA (Routing

and Switching)

Soft skills: Scrum/Agile methodology, Quick learner, Teamwork, Empathy, Dependability

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Tax Organization	May 2019- July 2020
Front End Developer	
• Tax Organization	Sept. 2013 - May 2019
System Analyst and IT Expert	
• DPI Co	Sept. 2010 - Sept 2013

Technical Support, install hardware and software, troubleshooting in the fields of hardware and software, networks and communication systems, Support for end devices in a networked environment.

• Iran Nara Co

Technical Support, install hardware and software, troubleshooting in the fields of hardware and software, networks and communication systems, Support for end devices in a networked environment.

July. 2008 - Sept 2010

PERSONAL WORKS

- Implemented responsive admin panel using Next.JS. Source Code: https://github.com/ab-prog1/Create-nextjs_Admin-panel-with-Laravel
- Implemented responsive online shopping website using Next.JS. Source Code: https://github.com/ab-prog1/Create-nextis eCommerce-with-Laravel
- Implemented responsive company website using React.JS. Source Code: https://github.com/ab-prog1/Education-Website-Using-ReactJS

EDUCATION

Master of Science, Software Engineering

Azad university North Tehran Branch, Tehran, Iran Sept. 2016 - Sept. 2018

Cumulative GPA: 18.73/20.0

THESIS: The Detection of Taxpayers with False Invoices using Data Mining Techniques.

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering

Azad university, khomein Branch, Khomein, Iran Sept. 2008- Oct. 2010

PUBLICATIONS

- Ghorbani A., Davoodi F., Zamanifar K. "Using type-2 fuzzy ontology to improve semantic interoperability for healthcare and diagnosis of depression," Artif Intell Med. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.artmed.2022.102452, 2022.
- Ghorbani A., Zamanifar K. "Type-2 fuzzy ontology-based semantic knowledge for indoor air quality assessment," Applied Soft Computing. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.asoc.2022.108658, 2022.
- Ghorbani A., Davoodi F., Layeghi K., "The Detection of Taxpayers with False Invoices using Data Mining Techniques" Tax J. 25, 167-193, 2017.

INTERESTS

Semantic Web, Semantic Web Services & Technologies, Ontology, OWL, RDF, Linked Data, Semantic Interoperability, semantic reasoning, Soft Computing, Fuzzy Theory, eHealth,

LANGUAGE

Persian (native) • German (B2) • English (A2)